A new red box which means news from Marymer and I received two new sets which I'm going to show you today.
I am wearing part of the outfit already because I wanted to try to put a catsuit underneath leggings to just use it as top which actually works pretty good.
Anyway, let's have a look in here.
Ah, with the gloves.
Next we have the Ari set which is a two piece set in red so Pandy and Bra and also the Nira
set which is a, which is not a set but a full body harness.
I love them, I already tried them so I want to show them to you.
let's start with this one. I just put on the top part to see how it looks with the leggings as a
normal outfit so not a lingerie version or a bedroom version but I think you could definitely
wear this out for a party or something as a bra on top of your normal clothes because it just looks
like a cool harness top I think it's a great look I love the shiny red leather
look here with the gold accessories so I probably need shoes with gold and
whatever but yeah let me put on the Pandy as well alright this is the full
set and I think it's so gorgeous I love the tone of red and as I already said I
of the shininess. I think it works super good together with the shiny cat suit.
And also I'm wearing a bra underneath but it's really like giving push-up
vibes with the harness here. Pulling the bra part to the neck. And I posted a
reel on Instagram already with this set and only underwear under it. So bra and
panties and there were a few people commenting like aren't you supposed to
wear it without underwear yes smarty pants you can also wear it without
underwear but we're still on social media if you want to see nude people go
to other home pages where you can find them but not on my channel and not on
Instagram or on YouTube it's like duh of course but as you can see here you can
also wear it with the catsuit or as a top as I've shown before so yeah love it
also like the combination with the heels red again so definitely one of my new
favorite harness sets it's really bold we have the open crotch panty here which
is not open crotch anymore due to the catsuit and yes I cannot really go to
the toilet with this outfit like that because I would have to unbress the
whole catsuit but this catsuit from Amoti also is available in a version
with an open crotch and then you could easily go to the toilet for example
anyway I think I will put this on now because it's completely different look
but also really nice this is the first one piece full body harness I have
from Marie More. I always say Marie More because it's a German pronunciation but
maybe it's Mary Mer. Probably both. Anyway the metal parts are silver this time. I
have a cuffs coming with this set which have these kind of linking parts so I
could if I could do this myself and they would be longer and I wouldn't have like
a slippery catsuit so they could be attached anywhere basically to the
harness which is kind of cool and you can like vary and like on the back to
yeah be creative with it I can show you some pictures when they're attached to
the bodysuit and the harness anyway I love again that this is slightly shiny
or that this is patent leather basically so shiny black leather it's great look
especially like the big big ring here because it's like an eye catcher if
you're not feeling like wearing only lingerie for example to a fetish party
or to kinky party I think this catsuit underneath which is slightly see-through
but also a catsuit itself is a great way to go out without showing too much skin
if you're not comfortable with it so I kind of love this combination also I'm
wearing size small but all the straps are adjustable which is pretty handy for
every body type anyway I hope you liked this video it's a short one but I just
wanted to show them to you real quick and yeah I'm quite happy with the looks
I think the red one is still my favorite but I love this one too
Mary Moore makes excellent quality and it just feels so elegant and like high
class so always happy to show them to you and now click on the subscribe
button and like this channel check out my patreon for additional content leave
a comment and yeah I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye